tokyoapps.us 2018-09-03

# Tokyoapps

### Privacy Policy 

LAST UPDATED: 1 May 2017 we operates this Site. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. Below instruction shows Privacy Policy for the Apps that you use on crickapps.com 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. 

vi.tokyoapps.us is concerned to protect the users privacy. The privacy policy is available to public at all times. We will notify you the changes made in the privacy policy in this page.   
Information we receive   
We collect information from third party sources predominantly Facebook.   
If you log in to vi.tokyoapps.us using Facebook we receive the following information.   
1\. Facebook username   
2\. Gender   
3\. Facebook profile picture   
We receive the information through Facebook consent box.   
Some apps requires the special permissions from the users.   
The information like public_profile, friends list, publish_actions can also be received by seeking the permission of users through Facebook consent box.   
Your information you provide to us is used only to generate the results for the games you play or the quizzes you take. We do not store your information on our server, nor we provide it to 3rd parties. 

**Cookies**   
www.vi.tokyoapps.us does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Links to external Websites

Our Applications may contain links to external websites of interest, especially through advertisements that we place. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that external website have thier own Terms & Policies. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.vi.tokyoapps.us.   
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.vi.tokyoapps.us and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....   
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.vi.tokyoapps.us send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.vi.tokyoapps.us has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.vi.tokyoapps.us's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### Controlling your Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

When you are asked to give permissions to access to your profile information, you may provide selected information or reject it completely by skipping Permissions. However, note that in such a case you may not be able to use our application at all, or to a limited functionality We will not distribute, sell or lease your personal information to any third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
